originpc.com 2019-07-25

# Privacy Policy | ORIGIN PC

* * *

ORIGIN PC knows that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

#### 1\. What Personal Information Do We Collect?

Information You Provide. We receive and store information you enter. For example, when you search for or buy a product or service, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you.

Cookies. Like many websites, we use "cookies". Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the "help" button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies.

Other Information: Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. Information from Other Sources. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This may include updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

#### 2\. How Do We Use Your Information?

Customized Shopping. We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience. As noted above, you may visit and shop anonymously without logging in. Agents. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Special Offers. We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to "opt-out" of receiving such offers.Â Law Enforcement. If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law. We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

#### 3\. How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list.

We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion.

We limit access to your information on a "need to know" basis.

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security. However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure.

#### 4\. Your Choice: Opt-in or Opt-out

It is your choice whether to receive emails or special offers from us and or if you wish for all of your data to be deleted or removed at any time. If you wish to not receive any emails or promotional offers from us, you may click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or you may contact marketing@originpc.com and we will notify you asap once your email has been removed. If you would like for us to remove/delete any or all other personal data such as your name, number, etc., please contact customerservice@originpc.com and an ORIGIN PC staff member will notify you once it has been removed.

#### 5\. Children

We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

#### 6\. Other Websites

Various Web sites may be linked to from this site. If you link to another site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site. We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy. Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others. You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance (www.privacyalliance.org).

#### 7\. Contact Us

If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, you may contact us at info@originpc.com.

We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future. If we do so, notice will be posted on our website.
